Corey Ingram C-817-808-1312 E-ci62009@gmail.com

Aledo, TX

Personal Statement:

I have demonstrated for over 22 years that I posses the attitude, drive, determination and ability to succeed at a very high level in business, sales, entrepreneurship, management and leadership. I have been married for 20 years, raised 4 beautiful children, actively participated in my community as well as continued to grow both professionally and personally.

Career Objective:

To obtain an executive IT/Software sales position with a growth oriented, progressive company. I want to apply my business development/sales skills in a entrepreneurial environment where I can make a significant impact.

Key Skills:

IT/Software/Hardware sales MSP Sales Network Management Cold Calling (Road Warrior)
Negotiating/Closing skills
Leader

Work Experience:

MeritCard Solutions - National IT/Software Sales Executive current

2006-

Responsible for cold calling via phone and face to face throughout the country to CEO'S, CFO'S, VP's and Business Owners (Acquired over 200 accounts)

Recruited, hired and trained a sales team including offering direction, activities, support, training and development of the team consisting of 25 people

Maintain relationships with existing clients to drive, up-sell and cross sell solutions and generate renewals (Over 90% client retention)

Consistently maintain aggressive revenue goals on a monthly, quarterly and annual basis (Closing ratio consistently over 40%)

RMM (Remote Monitoring & Management) of Servers and Workstations - Support for all Microsoft operating systems starting with Win7 and Server 2008 - Backup administration using local and cloud based storage options - Administration of Anti-Virus protection - Assistance with hardware warranty issues - Review of computer and network health

Desktops: maintain optimal desktop performance • Operating System administration • Virus protection administration • Print functionality • Error Log review • Microsoft Office accessibility and administration • Backup specified data locally and off-site

Servers: maintain optimal server performance • Operating System administration • Virus protection administration • Active Directory • Terminal Server Access • User administration • Hardware administration • Error Log review • Backup specified data

Principal Financial Group - Financial Representative

2005-2007

Provided professional financial advice through a consultative sales approach to business owners and accredited investors offering investment strategies including stocks, mutual funds, annuities and other complex financial products

Developed a business network through aggressive cold calling, face to face and phone selling as well as networking (Closing ratio over 40%)

Graduated from the "Principal Financial Advisory School"

Earned a series 6, 65 and Health and Life Insurance license

Cracor, Inc. - Managing Partner

1997-2005

Founded and operated the company form 1997 to 2005

Grew the company sales from Zero to Four million in gross annual sales

Developed relationships and negotiated contracts with Fortune

500 companies through networking, cold calling and consistent follow up over a 1-24 month sales cycle

Recruited, hired, trained and managed the sales team and office staff of 20 people Business development through networking, face to face and phone selling, marketing, presenting, preparing proposals, closing deals and managing the company

Practiced general business intelligence, including being strategic, tactical, competitive and doing whatever it took to be successful and close the deal

RSG, Inc. - Sales Executive

1995-1997

Responsible for estimating and selling commercial roofing materials to building owners, real estate companies, architects and commercial roofing companies

Blue print, manufacturer specification and architectural specification reading and takeoff capabilities

Developed a new distribution market in Oklahoma by networking with influential Building Owners, Real-Estate companies, Architects and some of the largest commercial Roofing contractors in the world

Major projects I sold including the largest mall in America at the time, Grapevine Mills Mall, Texas Motor Speedway, Dallas County Correctional Facility (Total sales over Fifteen Million Dollars)

OMG, Inc. - Regional Sales Representative

1993-1995

Responsible for the sales and distribution of commercial building and roofing materials through OEM channels, Independent Sales Representatives, Distributors and Architects over a 10 state territory

National salesman of the year 1993 (Out of 52 sales people)

Increased revenue in my region by 100% in year one

Increased regional distribution by 30%

Education:

Oklahoma University
Business Administration

UTA

Business

TCJC

Basics

1986-1992